Guide to the Richard Nash Gould Collection of Photographs Documenting Yale University
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Richard Nash Gould collection of photographs documenting Yale University
2013-2015
RU 1127
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
4
2 box
5891
This collection consists of photographic prints and digital images of Yale and New Haven buildings and locales, Yale football games, and other events.
Gould, Richard Nash
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of photographic prints and digital images of Yale and New Haven buildings and locales, Yale football games, and other events.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Richard Nash Gould, 2013 and 2015.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged alphabetically.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
General
Forms part of Yale Record Group 48-A (YRG 48-A), Yale pictorial records and collections.
Photographs; Gould, Richard Nash; Yale University -- Football; Yale University. Art Gallery
- Inventory, 2013; Accession 2014-A-053
  - Photographic prints
    - Cross Campus, 2012 September 15 (Box 1)
    - Friends of Yale gathering on Nantucket, 2013 August 4 (Box 1)
    - Hillhouse Avenue, 2012 May 21 (Box 1)
    - Levin, Richard, final speech at Woolsey Hall as President of Yale, 2013 December 6 (Box 1)
    - Old Campus
      - 2012 Sep 15 (Box 1)
      - 2001 May (Box 1)
    - Whiffenpoofs, performance at the Class of 1968 45th reunion, 2013 June 1 (Box 1)
    - Yale Art Gallery, 2013-2013
      - 2013 Nov 23 (Box 1)
      - 2012 Apr 28 (Box 1)
    - Yale football games
      - Yale vs. Army, 1923 November 5 (Box 1)
      - Yale vs. Harvard
        - 1914 November 21 (Box 1)
        - 2001 November 24 (Box 1)
        - 2007 November 17 (Box 1)
        - 2009 November 21 (Box 1)
        - 2011 November 19 (Box 1)
        - 2013 November 23 (Box 1)
    - Yale Glee Club concert, 2013 December 6 (Box 1)
  - Digital images, 37 digital image files (TIFF). (Box 2–4)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Original born digital files, as well as preservation masters, may not be accessed due to their fragility. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist request that they be made. Born digital files cannot be accessed remotely. System requirements include a Manuscripts and Archives computer and file viewing software.
    - College and Chapel Streets, New Haven
      - 2001 Mar
      - 1901
    - Cross Campus, 2012 September 15
    - Friends of Yale gathering on Nantucket, 2013 August 4
    - Hewitt Memorial Quadrangle, 2001 May
    - Hillhouse Avenue
      - 2012 May 31
      - 2012 May 21
    - Levin, Richard, final speech at Woolsey Hall as President of Yale, 2013 June 1
    - Mory's (2 images), 2009 June
    - Old Campus, 2012 September 15
      - 2012 Sep 15 (2 images), 2012-2012
      - 2001 May, 2001-2001
    - Saybrook College, 2013 November 23
    - Whiffenpoofs, performance at the Class of 1968 45th reunion, 2013 June 1
    - Whiffenpoofs, rehearsal at the Class of 1968 45th reunion, 2013 May 31
    - Yale football games
      - Yale vs. Army, 1923 November 5
      - Yale vs. Harvard
        - 1914 Nov 21, 1914-1914
        - 2001 Nov 24, 2001-2001
        - 2007 Nov 17, 2007-2007
        - 2009 Nov 21, 2009-2009
        - 2011 Nov 19, 2011-2011
        - 2013 Nov 23, 2013-2013
      - Yale Art Gallery
        - 2013 Nov 23, 2013-2013
        - 2012 Apr 28, 2012-2012
    - Yale Club of New York City tap room, 2013 December 6
    - Yale Corporation board room, 2012 September 15
    - Yale Glee Club concert, 2013 December 6
    - Yale Global Alumni Leadership Exchange (YaleGALE) event in Edinburgh, Scotland (6 photographs), 2011 March
    - Yankee Doodle Coffee Shop, 2001
- Additional material, 2014-2015; Accession 2016-A-001
  - Photographic prints, 2014-2015 (Box 1, Folder 1)